mydepotusa.com 2015-12-26

# MyUSWarehouse - Privacy Policy

### **Privacy Policy**

_**Updated 5th Jan 2013**_

##### **1\. Overview**

In order to operate the MyDepotUSA service and to reduce the risk of fraud, MyDepotUSA must ask you to provide us information about yourself and your credit card that you register with us. This Privacy Policy describes the information MyDepotUSA collects and how MyDepotUSA uses that information. MyDepotUSA takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. MyDepotUSA will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Section 4 below, there are circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on the http:www.MyDepotUSA.com website and its sub domain, where the services are offered by MyDepotUSA. By accepting the Privacy Policy and User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the MyDepotUSA User Agreement. Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not register for the MyDepotUSA service. 

MyDepotUSA reserves the right to amend, vary, delete or add to any of these terms of use from time to time without notice, and the amended terms of use shall apply. This Agreement is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering Users, and is otherwise effective from November 01, 2004 for all Users.

##### **2\. Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our service and MyDepotUSA asks that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

##### **3\. Information MyDepotUSA Collects**

**Required Information**  
To open a MyDepotUSA account, User must provide User's name, mobile phone number, e-mail and/or social network account information. This required information is necessary for us to carry out our verification procedures, process transactions, issue a new password if User forgets or loses User's password and to contact User should the need arise in administering User's account. 

**Transaction Information**  
When User uses MyDepotUSA to purchase merchandise or services from someone else, MyDepotUSA asks User to provide information related to each transaction, including the transaction amount and a brief description of the purchase. MyDepotUSA retains this information for each of User's transactions through MyDepotUSA. MyDepotUSA also collects the Internet address (IP address) of the computer or device User uses to access User's MyDepotUSA account, in order to help detect possible instances of unauthorized transactions. To facilitate customs declarations when MyDepotUSA couriers User's purchases to User, MyDepotUSA will disclose information of User's purchase to the relevant authorities on User's behalf. 

**Additional Verification**  
User's MyDepotUSA password and mobile phone PIN are to be used when operating User's MyDepotUSA service only. User should also not disclose User's MyDepotUSA password except when operating User's account with MyDepotUSA. 

**Customer Service Correspondence**  
If you send us correspondence, including e-mails and faxes, we retain such information in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from MyDepotUSA to you. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our User Agreement. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law. 

**Questionnaires, Surveys and Profile Data**  
From time to time, MyDepotUSA offers optional questionnaires and surveys to our Users for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing Users' interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in detail in the survey itself. If MyDepotUSA collects personally identifiable information from our Users in these questionnaires and surveys, the Users will be given notice of how the information will be used prior to their participation in the survey or questionnaire.

##### **4\. Our Use and Disclosure of Information**

**Internal Uses**  
MyDepotUSA collects, stores and processes User's personal information on our servers. MyDepotUSA uses the information MyDepotUSA collects about User in order 1) to provide our services and process User's transactions, 2) to provide customer service, 3) to determine User's eligibility to receive offers for special features or products. 

**Disclosure to Third Parties**  
MyDepotUSA will not share any of User's personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, or with User's express permission. These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared.

  * MyDepotUSA shares information with companies that help us process the transactions User has requested and protects our customers' transactions from fraud, such as sharing User's credit card number with a service that screens for lost and stolen card numbers. MyDepotUSA discloses information that MyDepotUSA in good faith believes is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our User Agreement.
  * MyDepotUSA discloses information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.
  * MyDepotUSA shares aggregated statistical data with our business partners or for public relations. For example, MyDepotUSA may disclose that a specific percentage of our Users live in Dallas.
  * MyDepotUSA shares your information with our parent, subsidiaries and joint ventures to help coordinate the services MyDepotUSA provides to you, enforce our terms of use, and promote trust and safety.

**Our Contacts with MyDepotUSA Customers**  
User's MyDepotUSA password and mobile phone PIN are to be used when operating User's MyDepotUSA service only. MyDepotUSA will never disclose this data to any third parties including User's bank and/ or credit card Company. User should also not disclose User's MyDepotUSA password except when operating User's account with MyDepotUSA. 

**Our Contacts with MyDepotUSA Customers**  
MyDepotUSA communicates with Users on a regular basis via e-mail to provide requested services, and MyDepotUSA also communicates by phone to resolve customer complaints or investigate suspicious transactions. MyDepotUSA uses User's e-mail address to confirm User's opening of a MyDepotUSA account, to send User notice of payments that User sends or receives through MyDepotUSA (including referral payments described below), to send information about important changes to our products and services, including the MyDepotUSA Periodical newsletter and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. 

**Internet Address Information**  
MyDepotUSA uses IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

##### **5\. Information Security**

User's credit card and account information are stored in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. MyDepotUSA restricts access to User's personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to User The security of User's MyDepotUSA account also relies on User's protection of User's MyDepotUSA password. User may not share User's MyDepotUSA password with anyone. MyDepotUSA will never ask User to send User's password or other sensitive information to us in an e-mail, though MyDepotUSA may ask User to enter this type of information on the MyDepotUSA website, which will always have a URL beginning with [https://www.MyDepotUSA.com/.](https://www.mydepotusa.com/) The padlock icon found in most browsers will appear locked and the first characters of the website address will change from "http" to "https" if User is accessing a secure server. 

Any e-mail or other communication requesting User's password, asking User to provide sensitive account information via email, or linking to a website with a URL that does not begin with [https://www.MyDepotUSA.com/](https://www.mydepotusa.com/) should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to MyDepotUSA immediately. If User does share MyDepotUSA password with a third party for any reason, including because the third party has promised to provide you additional services such as account aggregation, the third party will have access to User's account and User's personal information, and User may be responsible for actions taken using User's password. If User believes someone else has obtained access to User's password, please change it immediately by logging in to User's account at [www.MyDepotUSA.com](http://www.mydepotusa.com/) and changing User's Profile settings.

##### **6\. Accessing and Changing User's Information**

User can review the personal information User has provided us with and make any desired changes to such information, or to the settings for User's MyDepotUSA account, at any time by logging in to User's account on the MyDepotUSA website and changing User's profile including User's password. User can also close User's account through the MyDepotUSA website. If User closes User's MyDepotUSA account, MyDepotUSA will mark User's account in our database as "Closed," but will keep User's account information in our database. This is necessary in order to deter fraud, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if User closes User's account, User's personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties.

##### **7\. Contacting Us**

If User has any questions about this privacy statement, MyDepotUSA's information practices, or User's dealings with MyDepotUSA, User can contact us by writing to us at Attn: Legal Dept. MyDepotUSA, send us an email at [biz@MyDepotUSA.com](mailto:biz@MyDepotUSA.com)

##### **IMPORTANT NOTICE**

When using MyDepotUSA' s services, you as "User", are agreeing, on your behalf and on behalf of anyone else with an interest in the shipment that the Terms of use shall apply from the time that MyDepotUSA accepts the shipment unless otherwise agreed in writing by an authorized officer of MyDepotUSA. User's statutory rights and entitlements under any defined service feature (for which additional payment has been made) are not affected.
